(Raj:)raising the roof like this...
(Howard:)We did raise the roof
that night.
(Raj:)Yeah, we totally did.
Why do rock stars
(Howard:)do drugs when this feels so great?
(chuckles)
♪ Why can't I recall
this song? ♪
♪ This is taking
far too long. ♪
♪ The urge to bang my
head against the wall ♪
♪ Again and again and again and
again and again is strong. ♪
(Leonard:)Put on some headphones.
♪ No ♪
♪ They make my earlobes sweat. ♪
Uh, sweetie, why don't
you take a break
(Penny:)and do something
else for a while?
(Sheldon:)There was a project I've
been thinking about starting.
(Penny:)Okay, great. What is it?
(Sheldon:)I'll show you.
(Sheldon:)Dear Crazy Future Sheldon,
(Sheldon:)you were driven mad
by an earworm.
(Sheldon:)Your mind,
once your most trusted asset,
(Sheldon:)is now a sack of parrots
and monkeys.
(Leonard:)So...
(Sheldon:)I'm going to tell you
everything you need to know.